danier.com 2019-01-30

# Privacy Policy – Danier

Privacy Policy

  1. Our Privacy Statement 
    * This Privacy Policy sets out how Ramhi Global Retails Inc. O/A **DANIER** and its subsidiaries and related bodies corporate (collectively referred to in this policy as " **DANIER** ", " **we** " or " **us** ") protects the privacy of your Personal Information (as defined below) and the basis on which any Personal Information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed and disclosed by us in connection with **DANIER** ’s websites, namely danier.com, purchases at our stores, and any other websites or mobile applications that contain a link to this privacy policy (each a “ **Service** ”).
    * **DANIER** is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and to ensuring that your Personal Information is processed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations (as amended or replaced from time to time) protecting the privacy of Personal Information in the jurisdictions in which we operate (" **Applicable Laws** "). For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, Personal Information means information that is about you as an identifiable individual. Danier will only collect, use, store, disclose and transfer your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, any related privacy notices and Applicable Laws. If a Danier website, product or service describes privacy practices applicable to specific types of information or in certain circumstances and those descriptions conflict with this Privacy Policy, those descriptions shall supersede this Privacy Policy.
    * Please read the following carefully to understand **DANIER** ’s views and practices regarding your Personal Information and how we will treat it. By using our Service, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree with the collection, use, storage, disclosure and transfer of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or withdraw your consent, you should not provide us with Personal Information or should notify us that you have withdrawn your consent.
    * **DANIER** does not knowingly collect information from people under the age of 16 without the consent of your parent or guardian, and does not target our websites and Service to children under 16.
    * This Privacy Policy was last updated on, and is effective as of June 1, 2018. ****   **DANIER** reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, revise, delete and update this Privacy Policy from time to time. **DANIER** will use reasonable endeavours to notify you in advance of any modifications to the terms of this Privacy Policy (e.g. by posting the revised policy with a new effective date and by publishing the information about such modification on its web page of the Service). If you do not agree with the modifications, revisions, deletions or updates, your exclusive remedy is to cease using the Service. By continuing to access or utilize the Service after those changes are made, you shall be deemed to have accepted and agreed to the changes.
  2. THE PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU 
    * The Service collects information from you in two ways: directly from your input and automatically through the Service’s technologies. 
      * **Personal Information you give us** : The types of Personal Information the Service collects directly from you may include the following as well as any other Personal Information type that we expressly ask you to enter and submit to us when using the Service: 
        * Contact information, such as your name and address;
        * billing address; and
        * payment information (e.g. credit card).
      * **Information DANIER collects about you** : In order to provide our Service via the Internet, we collect the following information from you: 
        * Internet Protocol (" **IP** ") address used to connect your computer to the Internet;
        * computer, device and connection information, such as browser type and version, operating system, mobile platform, screen resolution, language, unique device identifier (“ **UDID** ”) and other technical identifiers;
        * uniform resource locator (" **URL** ") click stream data, including date and time, title of web page, and content you viewed or searched for on a Service; and
        * location information for any of our location-aware Service to provide you with more relevant content for where you are in the world.
      * **Cookies and Web Beacons** : The Service may also automatically collect information through the use of cookies or similar technologies, such as web beacons.  Cookies are small text files that a website sends to the browser on your computer or mobile device when you first visit a web page so that the website can recognize your device the next time you visit. In general, cookies, web beacons and similar technologies do not contain personally identifiable information, but when you furnish your personal information through the Service, this information may be linked to the non-personally identifiable data stored in cookies sent to your browser from the Service. 
        * **DANIER** and our service providers use these technologies for various purposes, including: facilitating the login process, administering, customizing and improving the Service, personalizing the browsing experience; advertising (including retargeting), promotions and surveys, reporting and tracking and analyzing user preferences and trends.
        * Our HTML-formatted emails may contain a web beacon to tell us whether our emails are opened and verify any clicks through to links or advertisements within the email. We may use this information for purposes including determining which of our emails are more interesting to users, to query whether users who do not open our emails wish to continue receiving them and to inform our advertisers in aggregate how many users have clicked on their advertisements. The web beacon will be deleted when you delete the email. Emails in plain text rather than HTML will not include the web beacon.
        * There are a number of ways to manage cookies. The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new browser cookie, and how to disable existing browser cookies.  However, if you block cookies, you may not be able to register, login or make full use of the Service. You can also use your mobile device’s settings to manage the available privacy options.
      * **Mobile Information** : We offer mobile applications which allow you to shop online, check product availability, learn about store events, or receive other information from us. All Personal Information collected via our mobile application is governed by this Privacy Policy. We, or our service providers, may also collect, use, or disclose Personal Information and other information from and about you on our mobile websites and through your interactions with us on your mobile device. This information may include a telephone number and mobile device identifier provided by your mobile device or wireless carrier, as applicable. You do not have to provide your location information to use our mobile applications however, store-specific services require a postal code to function and we will save your postal code for future reference. When you download our mobile application, you may choose to allow it to obtain your precise location. In this case, we will determine your postal code from the precise location data received from your mobile device. We do not store precise location data; we only store the postal codes associated with the location. Our mobile applications offer automatic (push) notifications. We will provide push notifications only to those who opt-in to receive them. If you have questions about location and notification privacy, please contact your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings. We may offer updated or enhanced versions of our mobile applications that include additional features created by us or using third party functionality. Our applications or the third party may automatically collect information about your precise location from your device, but only if you allow it.
    * In the event that you have submitted Personal Information about another individual to us, you represent and warrant that you have obtained any and all consent required by Applicable Laws to do so.
  3. WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION 
    * **DANIER** (and third-party data processors who may be acting on our behalf) may collect, use, store and process your Personal Information described above for the following purposes: 
      * to present the Service to you;
      * to administer and operate the Service, including allowing you to register an account with us, to process payments and returns and to respond to your questions, enquiries, complaints or verify instructions from you;
      * to process and fulfill your order, including to send you e-mails to confirm your order status and shipment;
      * to improve the contents of our Service, including to customize the content, advertising and/or layout of websites;
      * conduct analytics to improve and enhance our Service, including marketing and promotion analysis and to help us learn more about your shopping preferences;
      * to contact you, including through e-mail, mail, telephone, through our website or any other manner, in respect of your use of the Service or for other marketing purposes (subject to any applicable laws or regulations);
      * to offer new products, services or programs to you, including through emails, promotions or contests (subject to any applicable laws or regulations);
      * to prevent and detect security threats, fraud or other malicious activity;
      * in any other way we may describe when you provide us with the Personal Information;
      * to the extent we have a legal obligation, right or duty under the Applicable Law to use or disclose your information (including for crime and fraud prevention, resolving disputes, enforcing our agreements or other related purposes);
      * to anonymize and aggregate the Personal Information for any other purposes, provided that no identifiable personal information can be readily identified; and
      * for any other purpose with your consent.
    * If we combine any automatically collected information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information.
    * **DANIER** will only retain your Personal Information for as long as reasonably necessary having regard to the purposes for which your Personal Information was collected and will delete or anonymize such Personal Information after the expiry of such period unless otherwise required under the Applicable Law. Any anonymized and aggregated information will be retained by Danier.
  4. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL information 
    * **DANIER** may share your Personal Information that it collects from you or that you provide to Danier with selected third parties for the following purposes: 
      * to operate and provide the Service or any other purposes as set out in paragraph 1 above; and
      * to enforce or apply any agreements between us and you, or to investigate potential breaches of such agreements.
    * **DANIER** may share your Personal Information with, without limitation: 
      * business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance, or their assistance with, of any contract we enter into with them or you or to provide you with the Service; and
      * companies that provide statistical analysis services.
    * **DANIER** will ensure that corporate third parties who have received Personal Information from us will maintain a comparable level of protection of the Personal Information as set out in this Privacy Policy by using contractual or other means and that any disclosed Personal Information will only be used for the purposes as set out in paragraph 1 above. To the fullest extent permitted by Applicable Law, **DANIER** excludes all liability arising from the use of your Personal Information by third parties. **DANIER** can, on request, confirm the name of each third party that Personal Information is, or will be, transferred to.
    * **DANIER** may also disclose Personal Information to third parties: (i) to comply with any applicable laws, regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas; (ii) to enforce or apply any agreements between us and you; (iii) to protect **DANIER** ’s rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of other users of the Service or others (e.g., for fraud protection etc.); or (iv) to resolve any disputes.
    * Except as set out in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose, sell, distribute, rent or lease your Personal Information to third parties unless we have your permission or to complete a transaction for you. We do not share your identifiable Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing use without your express consent.
    * In the event that a third party proposes to acquire all or some of our business and/or assets, we may disclose your Personal Information to that third party in connection with their proposed or actual acquisition. In the event that we become insolvent or we are in any similar situation, we may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties as part of a business or asset sale carried out where such disclosure is lawful and compliant with the Applicable Laws.
  5. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF DATA

5.1           **DANIER** may transfer your Personal Information to our overseas related entities, subsidiaries, related bodies corporate and franchisees in order to provide the Service. It may also be necessary for us to disclose your Personal Information to third parties located in Canada or the United States of America or outside of North America in connection with the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

5.2           By submitting your Personal Information you consent to the transfer, disclosure, storage and/or processing of your Personal Information outside the jurisdiction in which the information was originally collected. **DANIER** will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your Personal Information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Where we have engaged international third parties to perform services in relation to the Service, we will use contractual or other means to ensure such third parties offer a comparable level of protection in respect of the Personal Information.

  6. SECURITY 
    * **DANIER** has in place security measures to store all Personal Information collected and received securely. We use appropriate technical, organizational, administrative and physical measures to protect your Personal Information contained in our system against accidental damage, deletion, misuse, loss and unauthorized access or alteration. Unfortunately, the collection, use and disclosure of information can’t be 100% secure and, accordingly, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information, including Personal Information, you disclose or transmit to us. However, we strive to protect your information and privacy.
    * If you have created an account with us, it is important that you create strong a password and that you keep it secret. Do not share your password with anyone, and never share it in response to an email or phone request, even if it appears to be from a trusted company or person.
  7. EXTERNAL LINKS 
    * When our service is available via the websites of our partners, those partners may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information. Their use of your Personal Information is governed by their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any other websites, even if you access them using links from our Service. We therefore recommend that you check the privacy policy of each site that you visit and make sure that you are comfortable with the terms of such policies before providing any Personal Information.
  8. YOUR RIGHTS 
    * You have the right to, at any time, ask us not to process or share your Personal Information for marketing purposes (even where you have previously given consent). **DANIER** will inform you (before collecting your Personal Information) if it intends to use your Personal Information for such purposes or if **DANIER** intends to disclose your Personal Information to any third party for such purposes (subject to obtaining your prior consent).
    * You have the right to access details of your Personal Information that we hold about you by written request and to request correction or rectification of such Personal Information, if the Applicable Laws allows you to do so. 
      * If you have registered an account with us, you may view and update your account information by logging into your account on our website or mobile application. Once logged in, you can view or update your contact information and/or your e-mail preferences regarding e-mails from us. You can also contact us to access or update your information. 
    * You may choose to no longer receive communications from us. You may unsubscribe to any email from us using the instructions in the communication you receive. Subject to applicable laws or regulations, this may not stop us from contacting you about your account or transactions with us or other information required for your use of the Service.
    * You also have the right to change your mind about consenting to the use, disclosure and transfer of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy by contacting us at the address listed below. If you withdraw your consent for **DANIER** to process your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, Danier may not be able to provide you with our entire Service.
    * You have the right to make a complaint about a possible breach of the Applicable Laws to us. We will consider any complaints we receive and respond to your complaint within a reasonable period of time. You also may lodge a complaint about the treatment of your Personal Information with the supervisory authority located in you jurisdiction, if the Applicable Laws allow you to do so.
    * You can exercise your rights as described in this Privacy Policy or under Applicable Laws above by contacting us at the address listed below.
  9. CONTACT 
    * Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [customercare@danier.com](mailto:customercare@danier.com) or to: ATTN: CUSTOMER CARE, **DANIER** , 7700 Keele Street Unit 4, Vaughan, Ontario L4K 2A1
